# ANAS ER-RAKIBI

### Engineering student in computer science

**L** +212 696486911 ∂ anas-dev.vercel.app @ errakibianasdev@gmail.com

Ouarzazate - Morocco

@ linkedin.com/in/anas-er-rakibi/

#### ☆ Single

## **ABOUT ME**

3rd year computer engineering student at SUPMTI school in Rabat, passionate Full Stack Web Developer with expertise in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, Laravel, Node.js, and Express.js. Dedicated to creating intuitive user interfaces and constantly up to date with the latest trends in web development. Strong problem-solving skills and a collaborative team spirit.

### **EXPERIENCES**

#### Operational training

#### Veneroo.ma

iii 01/2024 - 02/2024 ♀ Ouarzazate, Morocco

- Development and maintenance of client websites using Laravel 8, MySQL and Bootstrap.
- · Optimizing website performance.
- Creation and implementation of new features.
- Development of a human resources management (HRM) website with Laravel 8, MySQL and Bootstrap.

#### Introductory Internship

#### Veneroo.ma

- iii 07/2023 08/2023 ♀ Ouarzazate, Maroc
- Development and maintenance of client websites using Laravel 8, MySQL and Bootstrap.
- Collaboration with multidisciplinary teams.
- Implementation of responsive design and cross-browser compatibility.
- Development of a medical website using Laravel 8, MySQL and Bootstrap.

#### Full Stack Web Developer

#### ISTA Ouarzazate - PFE

iii 03/2024 - 05/2024 ♀ Ouarzazate, Maroc

- Design and development of an integrated SaaS platform for the management of vocational training establishments: D-EFP (Digital Vocational Training
- Final year project (PFE) using Laravel 10, MySQL, JavaScript, and Bootstrap 5.
- Features for managing registrations, timetables, trainers, directors (pedagogical, establishment, regional), and educational resources.

#### Full Stack Web Developer

## Freelance, Dmenu - Restaurant Management Application

- # 08/2024 Present Maroc
- Customer Interface: Creation of a user-friendly interface for taking orders, facilitating the user experience.
- Dashboard: Design of a dashboard for menu management, allowing the addition, modification and deletion of items.
- Order Management: Integrating functionality to track and manage customer orders in real-time.

## **EDUCATION**

## 3rd year of the computer engineering cycle

## **SupMTI**

苗 10/2024 - Present

Rabat, Morocco

Technician specializing in digital development

## **Specialized Institute of Applied Technology-ISTA**

**=** 09/2022 - 07/2024

Ouarzazate, Morocco

Biology-Chemistry-Geology (B-C-G)

#### **FSTG Marrakech**

**=** 10/2021 - 01/2022

Marrakech, Morocco

### Bachelor's degree in Life and Earth Sciences - SVT

## **ABOU BAKR SEDDIK High School**

## **PROJECTS**

#### Movie website

Creation of a movie site in ReactJS with a Landing Page designed in Tailwind CSS.

#### F-commerce website

Development of an e-commerce website in Bootstrap 5, JQuery, PHP, MySQL and integration of Stripe for online payment.

### Internal management platform

Design of an internal management platform for an establishment in HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap 5, PHP, JavaScript, and MySQL.

#### Library Management Platform

Development of a library management platform in PHP, MySQL, and Bootstrap 5.

#### **SKILLS**

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, PHP

Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS

Laravel Framework, React.js, Express.js

MySQL, MongoDB

Azure DevOps, Git

Microsoft Word, Microsoft Power Point, Microsoft Excel

## SOFT SKILLS

**Time management** 

**Autonomy** 

**Teamwork** 

## **LANGUES**

Arabe Native

**Français** 

intermediate

**Anglais** 

intermediate

# **CERTIFICATS**

Python-PICAP: Cisco

JavaScript essential 1: Cisco

Agile Scrum Master: Simplilearn